Guide to the Time Inc. Time-Life News Service Records 1935-1987 MS 3009-RG 14
New-York Historical Society
- Series I. Chief of Correspondent Files, 1935-1987; 60.5 Linear feet in 60 record cartons, 1 flat box
  - Subseries I.E. Bureau Files, 1935-1984; 9.4 Linear feet in 11 record cartons
    - Johannesburg [RESTRICTED], 1979-1982 (Offsite-box R46)
    - London, 1943-1951, 1979-1983 (Offsite-box 3193, Folder 3-11)
    - London [RESTRICTED], 1981 (Offsite-box R46)
    - London: Fortune, 1950-1954 (Offsite-box 3193, Folder 12)
    - London: Time, 1950-1953 (Offsite-box 3193, Folder 13-15)
    - Los Angeles, 1957-1961, 1979-1985 (Offsite-box 3193, Folder 16-19)
    - Madrid, 1952-1956, 1962-1963, 1969 (Offsite-box 3194, Folder 1-5)
    - Madrid: Life, 1955-1956 (Offsite-box 3194, Folder 6)
    - Madrid: Sports Illustrated, 1955-1956 (Offsite-box 3194, Folder 7)
    - Mediterranean, 1970 (Offsite-box 3194, Folder 8)
    - Melbourne, 1980-1983 (Offsite-box 3194, Folder 9)
    - Melbourne [RESTRICTED], 1983 (Offsite-box R46)
    - Mexico, 1945-1968, 1975-1984 (Offsite-box 3194, Folder 10-14)
    - Mexico: Life, 1952-1954 (Offsite-box 3194, Folder 15)
    - Mexico [RESTRICTED], 1983 (Offsite-box R46)
    - Mexico: Personnel, 1962-1963 (Offsite-box 3194, Folder 16)
    - Mexico: Time, 1950-1954 (Offsite-box 3194, Folder 17)
    - Mexico City, 1944-1958 (Offsite-box 3194, Folder 18-21)
    - Mexico City: Life, 1950-1951 (Offsite-box 3194, Folder 22)
    - Miami, 1957-1970 (Offsite-box 3194, Folder 23-26)
    - Miami [RESTRICTED], 1961 (Offsite-box R46)
    - Miami: Life, 1963 (Offsite-box 3194, Folder 27)
    - Miami: Personnel, 1964-1967 (Offsite-box 3194, Folder 28)
    - Middle East: Crisis: July 1958 (Offsite-box 3194, Folder 29)
    - Montreal, 1957-1971 (Offsite-box 3194, Folder 30-31)
    - Montreal, 1969-1974 (Offsite-box 3195, Folder 1)
    - Montreal [RESTRICTED], 1974 (Offsite-box R46)
    - Montreal: Personnel, 1963-1973 (Offsite-box 3195, Folder 2)
    - Montreal: Personnel [RESTRICTED], 1968 (Offsite-box R46)
    - Moscow, 1944-1973, 1979-1983 (Offsite-box 3195, Folder 3-10)
    - Moscow [RESTRICTED], 1981 (Offsite-box R46)
    - Moscow: Expulsion, 1958-1965 (Offsite-box 3195, Folder 11-12)
    - Moscow: Proposed Businessmen'a Trip: 1968 May (Offsite-box 3195, Folder 13)
    - Nairobi, 1962, 1979-1984 (Offsite-box 3195, Folder 14-16)
    - Nairobi [RESTRICTED], 1983 (Offsite-box R46)
    - New Delhi, 1952-1962, 1982-1985 (Offsite-box 3195, Folder 17-22)
    - New Delhi, 1979-1983 (Offsite-box 3196, Folder 1)
    - New Delhi [RESTRICTED], 1980-1985 (Offsite-box R46)
    - New Delhi: Life, 1954-1959 (Offsite-box 3196, Folder 2-3)
    - New Delhi: Press Law, 1955-1957 (Offsite-box 3196, Folder 4-5)
    - New Delhi: Slick, 1957 (Offsite-box 3196, Folder 6-7)
    - New Delhi: Time, 1952-1954 (Offsite-box 3196, Folder 8)
    - New Delhi and Bombay, 1946-1951 (Offsite-box 3196, Folder 9-10)
    - New York, 1952-1962, 1980-1983 (Offsite-box 3196, Folder 11-13)
    - New York [RESTRICTED], 1962 (Offsite-box R46)
    - Ottawa, 1956-1961, 1979-1983 (Offsite-box 3196, Folder 14-16)
    - Pacific and China-Burma-India Theater: 1943-1944, 1943-1946, 1955, 1965 (Offsite-box 3196, Folder 17)
    - Panama, 1952-1954 (Offsite-box 3196, Folder 18)
    - Panama: Life, 1952-1954 (Offsite-box 3196, Folder 19)
    - Panama: Time, 1951-1954 (Offsite-box 3196, Folder 20)
    - Rio: Local Paid Staff, 1977-1983 (Offsite-box 3196, Folder 21-22)
    - Rio: Local Paid Staff [RESTRICTED], 1983 (Offsite-box R46)
    - Rome, 1979-1983 (Offsite-box 3196, Folder 23)
    - Rome [RESTRICTED], 1979-1981 (Offsite-box R46)
    - San Francisco, 1979-1983 (Offsite-box 3196, Folder 24)
    - San Francisco [RESTRICTED], 1983 (Offsite-box R46)
    - Tokyo, 1979-1983 (Offsite-box 3196, Folder 25)
    - Tokyo [RESTRICTED], 1982 (Offsite-box R46)
    - Washington D.C., 1979-1983 (Offsite-box 3196, Folder 26)
    - Washington D.C., 1978-1981 (Offsite-box 3197, Folder 1)
    - Washington D.C. [RESTRICTED], 1982 (Offsite-box R46)
- Series II. New York Regional Bureau Chief and Senior Correspondent Laurence I. Barrett Files, 1975-1980; 0.2 Linear feet in 9 folders
  Laurence I. Barrett, better known as Larry, first shows up in Time Inc.'s department heads lists in February 1970. At this time, Barrett was working as a senior editor at Time. Barret remained in this position until 1978 when he was promoted to New York regional bureau chief. By 1979, Barrett is no longer a bureau chief and has become a senior correspondent for the Time-Life News Service. He remains in this position through at least 1983. From 1984 forward, Barrett no longer shows up on department heads lists.
  The New York Regional Bureau Chief and Senior Correspondent Laurence I. Barrett Files cover the period of 1975 to 1980 and cover both his freelance work and Time political coverage. While these materials were originally housed with research for a variety of stories on Chappaquiddick, Barrett's materials appeared to be unrelated and were removed to be rehoused. Contained in this series are photographs, dispatches, clippings, notes, drafts, and correspondence.
  - Articles, 1975-1980 (Offsite-box 3197, Folder 2-4)
  - Articles [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Offsite-box R46)
  - Miscellaneous, 1965-1980, undated (Offsite-box 3197, Folder 5-6)
  - Photos, 1978-1979 (Offsite-box 3197, Folder 7)
  - Young, Andy, 1976-1977 (Offsite-box 3197, Folder 8-9)
- Series III. Financial Files, 1956-1962, 1970-1985; 5.95 Linear feet in 7 record cartons
  Historical Note
  Through 1974, Time-Life News Service's finances were handled by staff within Time's business office and were mainly overseen by an assistant manager. After 1974, Time-Life News Service had their own business office, but the department does not show up on department head lists in the Time Inc. Reference Files until 1987. Between 1974 and 1987, those who work on the Time-Life New Service finances are not named on department head lists.
  Notable business department staff include Emily Friedrich, Linda Vartoogian, and Camille Cassata. Emily Friedrich does not appear in any department heads lists. Linda Vartoogian is listed in 1972 and 1974 as an assistant to Time's business manager but disappears from the lists after that even though she continues to work on the news service finances until at least 1983. Camille Cassata only appears on the 1987 departments heads list as the news service's financial manager, but the materials themselves indicate she may have been working for the news service as early as 1983.
  Citation:
  Time Inc. Reference Files, MS 3009-RG 3, New-York Historical Society.
  Financial Files cover the period of 1956 to 1985 and contain materials related to the Time-Life News Service's finances. The majority of materials featured in this series were collected by Emily Friedrich, Linda Vartoogian, and Camille Cassata, also called Camille Sanabria after she was married, who appear to have worked in Time's Business Office and Time-Life News Service's business office. A variety of chiefs of correspondents appear in the records along with business office staff. Unlike other parts of Time Inc. that kept financial and editorial departments as separate, the Time-Life News Service had more overlap with chiefs of correspondents also overseeing the department's finances. The main chiefs of correspondents who were involved in business department affairs were Richard Clurman, Lawrence Laybourne, James Shepley, Emmet Hughes, Murray Gart, and Dick Duncan.
  Included in this series are budget reports, operating statements, financial statements, lists of salary account, bureau financial reports, Washington Star Payment Reports, contracts, lease agreements, clippings, newsletters, Time mastheads, receipts, notes, copies of checks, invoices, photos, negatives, itinerary, fee requisition forms, and correspondence. The correspondence included in this series discuss expenses, budgets, finances, committee meetings, expenditures, travel, allowances, fees, costs, raises, utility costs, financial payouts, financial issues, salaries, severance pay, visas, refugees eligibility, grocery costs, food stamps, doctor's appointments, money requisitions, contact info, and bureau updates.
  Included in this series are two files on the Washington Star. These files provide information about the Washington Star's financial relationship with the Time-Life News Service as well as the newspaper's dependency on the Time-Life News Service for acquiring information news.
  - Budget, 1956-1962 (Offsite-box 3197, Folder 10-18)
  - Budget, 1974-1977 (Offsite-box 3198, Folder 1-6)
  - Budget: Reports: 1974 Feb. - 1976 June, 1974-1976 (Offsite-box 3198, Folder 7-15)
  - Budget: Reports: 1976 July - 1980 June, 1976-1980 (Offsite-box 3199, Folder 1-12)
  - Housing Allowances, 1981-1984 (Offsite-box 3199, Folder 13)
  - Housing Allowances, 1970-1983 (Offsite-box 3200, Folder 1-4)
  - Housing Allowances [RESTRICTED], 1974-1984 (Offsite-box R46)
  - Local Staff, 1972-1979 (Offsite-box 3200, Folder 5-12)
  - Operating Costs: Paris Bureau, 1979-1985 (Offsite-box 3200, Folder 13-16)
  - Operating Costs: Paris Bureau [RESTRICTED], 1979-1983 (Offsite-box R46)
  - Reconciliations, 1983-1984 (Offsite-box 3200, Folder 17-18)
  - Re-Estimates, 1980-1981 (Offsite-box 3200, Folder 19-20)
  - Re-Estimates, 1976-1985 (Offsite-box 3201, Folder 1-13)
  - Seng, Hout, 1980-1983 (Offsite-box 3201, Folder 14-15)
  - Seng, Hout [RESTRICTED], 1981 (Offsite-box R46)
  - Transfer Bill, 1981-1983 (Offsite-box 3201, Folder 16-17)
  - Transfer Bills, 1983-1986 (Offsite-box 3202, Folder 1-4)
  - Vietnamese Refugees, 1975-1985 (Offsite-box 3202, Folder 5-7)
  - Vietnamese Refugees [RESTRICTED], 1975, 1985 (Offsite-box R46)
  - Washington Star, 1978-1981 (Offsite-box 3202, Folder 8-11)
  - Washington Star: Fees, 1981 (Offsite-box 3202, Folder 12-13)
  - Year End Close: 1976-1979, 1975-1980 (Offsite-box 3202, Folder 14-18)
  - Year End Close [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Offsite-box R46)
- Series IV. Staff Files, 1936-1987; 46.8 Linear feet in 49 record cartons
  The Staff Files contain personnel and biographical files assembled on employees of the Time-Life News Service. These materials within these files were gathered by a variety of staff with the Time-Life News Service such as the business department, chiefs of correspondents, and deputy chiefs of correspondents. The records within this series cover the period of 1936 through 1987. Included in this series are payroll forms, dispatches, photographs, negatives, visa applications, clippings, job applications, timecards, article drafts, post cards, expense reports, allowance forms, benefit claims forms, receipts, invoices, itinerary, biographical data forms, writing samples, check requisition forms, CVs, resumes, college transcripts, list of job candidates, budget reports, reference letters, query sheets, personnel forms, cost of living reports, department of defense accreditation forms, press releases, vacation schedule forms, disability forms, work and rate records, purchase order forms, inventory forms, insurance forms, entry forms, birth certificates, and correspondence.
  Arranged into three subseries:
  Subseries IV.A. General Files
  Subseries IV.B. Ex-Staff Files
  Subseries IV.C. Stringer Files
  - Subseries IV.A. General Files, 1936-1987; 26.6 Linear feet in 29 record cartons
    The General Files covers the period of 1936 to 1987 and contain a mix of biographical and personnel files for Time-Life News Service staff, correspondents, and bureau chiefs. Due to the way that the materials are organized, it is unclear who collected or organized the materials. The files included in this subseries include a mix of staff that were currently working for Time-Life News Service when the files were transferred to the archives as well as files for ex-staff and stringers. If a box appeared to have files mainly for ex-staff or stringers then those boxes were separated and placed into their appropriate subseries. The remaining materials do not offer any indication of their original organization and have been interfiled into one subseries. While there are separate series for ex-staff and stringers, people that fall into those categories may be found in this subseries as well.
    Included in this series are payroll forms, dispatches, photos, negative, visa applications, clippings, job applications, timecards, article drafts, post cards, expense reports, allowance forms, benefit claims forms, receipts, invoices, itinerary, biographical data forms, writing samples, check requisition forms, CVs, resumes, college transcripts, list of job candidates, budget reports, reference letters, query sheets, personnel forms, cost of living reports, department of defense accreditation forms, press releases, vacation schedule forms, disability forms, work and rate records, purchase order forms, inventory forms, insurance forms, entry forms, birth certificates, and correspondence. The correspondence included in this series discusses vacations, retirements, raises, overtime, travel, visas, job offers, story suggestions, taxes, allowances, stringers, salaries, communication issues, expenses, advances, debts, office arrangements, insurance, exchange rates, masthead changes, employment verifications, vacations, housing, resignations, bureau transfers, appliance purchases, immigration, revenue, leaves of absence, and meetings.
    - General News Service Staff, 1936-1941, 1947-1949 (Offsite-box 3203, Folder 1)
    - Abell, George, 1956-1957 (Offsite-box 3203, Folder 2)
    - Abramson, Jill [RESTRICTED], 1975-1977 (Offsite-box R46)
    - Ackerman, Gordon, 1962 (Offsite-box 3203, Folder 3)
    - Ades, Edouard I., 1969-1974 (Offsite-box 3203, Folder 4)
    - Agics, Steven, 1957 (Offsite-box 3203, Folder 5)
    - Aikman, David, 1965-1982 (Offsite-box 3203, Folder 6-8)
    - Aikman, David [RESTRICTED], 1966-1980 (Offsite-box R46)
    - Aikman, David: Mongolia Trip, 1974-1977 (Offsite-box 3203, Folder 9)
    - Aikman, David: Mongolia Trip [RESTRICTED], 1974 (Offsite-box R46)
    - Ajemian, Robert, 1960-1962, 1975-1984 (Offsite-box 3203, Folder 10)
    - Ajemian, Robert [RESTRICTED], 1977-1984 (Offsite-box R46)
    - Alexander, John, 1966-1967 (Offsite-box 3203, Folder 11)
    - Alexander, John [RESTRICTED], 1966 (Offsite-box R46)
    - Alexander, Roy, 1951 (Offsite-box 3203, Folder 12)
    - Alig, Wallace, 1945-1946 (Offsite-box 3203, Folder 13)
    - Allis, Sam, 1976-1982 (Offsite-box 3203, Folder 14-15)
    - Allis, Sam [RESTRICTED], 1981-1982 (Offsite-box R46)
    - Aloba, Abiodum, 1960 (Offsite-box 3203, Folder 16)
    - Altman, Jack, 1964-1967 (Offsite-box 3203, Folder 17)
    - Altman, Jack [RESTRICTED], 1965-1967 (Offsite-box R46)
    - Anderson, Alan, 1969-1972 (Offsite-box 3203, Folder 18)
    - Anderson, Alan [RESTRICTED], 1969-1972 (Offsite-box R46)
    - Anderson, Jon, 1960-1966 (Offsite-box 3203, Folder 19)
    - Angelo, Bonnie, 1966-1982 (Offsite-box 3203, Folder 20)
    - Angelo, Bonnie [RESTRICTED], 1967-1982 (Offsite-box R46)
    - Angus, Anne Denny, 1958-1961 (Offsite-box 3203, Folder 21)
    - Anson, Robert, 1967-1971 (Offsite-box 3203, Folder 22-24)
    - Anson, Robert [RESTRICTED], 1969-1974 (Offsite-box R46)
    - Anson, Robert: Capture, 1970-1975 (Offsite-box 3203, Folder 25-26)
    - Antcliffe, Herbert, 1940-1946 (Offsite-box 3203, Folder 27)
    - Applegate, Clara, 1949, 1959-1970 (Offsite-box 3203, Folder 28)
    - Applegate, Clare [RESTRICTED], 1955, 1968-1969 (Offsite-box R46)
    - Arguello, Anibal, 1956 (Offsite-box 3203, Folder 29)
    - Attinger, Joelle, 1977-1982 (Offsite-box 3203, Folder 30)
    - Attinger, Joelle [RESTRICTED], 1979-1982 (Offsite-box R46)
    - Atwater, Jim, undated (Offsite-box 3203, Folder 31)
    - Atwater, Lucille E., 1962 (Offsite-box 3203, Folder 32)
    - Auer, Bernhard M., 1963-1969 (Offsite-box 3203, Folder 33)
    - Auerbach, Minna, 1973 (Offsite-box 3203, Folder 34)
    - Auerbach, Minna [RESTRICTED], 1972 (Offsite-box R46)
    - Austin, John, 1969-1978 (Offsite-box 3204, Folder 1)
    - Austin, John [RESTRICTED], 1970-1978 (Offsite-box R46)
    - B: Miscellaneous, 1949-1950 (Offsite-box 3204, Folder 2)
    - Bailey, Ron, 1977 (Offsite-box 3204, Folder 3)
    - Baker, Edgar, 1969 (Offsite-box 3204, Folder 4)
    - Baldessari, Martin, 1973 (Offsite-box 3204, Folder 5)
    - Baldessari, Martin [RESTRICTED], 1973 (Offsite-box R47)
    - Balfour, Honor, 1947-1973 (Offsite-box 3204, Folder 6-8)
    - Banta, Kenneth, 1981-1982 (Offsite-box 3204, Folder 9)
    - Banta, Kenneth [RESTRICTED], 1980-1982 (Offsite-box R47)
    - Barco. James, 1962 (Offsite-box 3204, Folder 10)
    - Barrett, Laurence, 1975-1983 (Offsite-box 3204, Folder 11)
    - Barrett, Laurence [RESTRICTED], 1975-1982 (Offsite-box R47)
    - Barrios, Juana Olga, 1982 (Offsite-box 3204, Folder 12)
    - Bavagnoli, Carlo, 1976-1977 (Offsite-box 3204, Folder 13)
    - Beakley, Kathleen, 1959-1970 (Offsite-box 3204, Folder 14)
    - Beakley, Kathleen [RESTRICTED], 1969-1971 (Offsite-box R47)
    - Beal, John, 1958-1970 (Offsite-box 3204, Folder 15)
    - Beal, John [RESTRICTED], undated (Offsite-box R47)
    - Beardwood, Roger, 1972-1978 (Offsite-box 3204, Folder 16-20)
    - Beardwood, Roger [RESTRICTED], 1971-1977 (Offsite-box R47)
    - Beaty, Jonathan, 1978-1984 (Offsite-box 3204, Folder 21)
    - Beaty, Jonathan [RESTRICTED], 1978-1982 (Offsite-box R47)
    - Beckwith, David, 1971-1984 (Offsite-box 3204, Folder 22-23)
    - Beckwith, David [RESTRICTED], 1971-1984 (Offsite-box R47)
    - Behr, Edward, 1961-1965 (Offsite-box 3204, Folder 24)
    - Benjamin, Robert, 1947-1951 (Offsite-box 3204, Folder 25)
    - Berges, Marshall, 1958-1969 (Offsite-box 3204, Folder 26)
    - Berges, Marshall [RESTRICTED], 1965-1968 (Offsite-box R47)
    - Bernier, Rosamund, 1952 (Offsite-box 3204, Folder 27)
    - Bernstein, Lester, 1952-1955 (Offsite-box 3204, Folder 28)
    - Berretty, Dominique, 1960-1961 (Offsite-box 3204, Folder 29)
    - Berry, Adrian, 1965-1966 (Offsite-box 3204, Folder 30)
    - Berry, Adrian [RESTRICTED], 1965 (Offsite-box R47)
    - Beshoar, Barron, 1962-1968 (Offsite-box 3204, Folder 31)
    - Birnbaum, Jesse, 1962-1972 (Offsite-box 3204, Folder 32)
    - Blunden, Godfrey, 1959-1964 (Offsite-box 3204, Folder 33)
    - Boeger, Barbara, 1969 (Offsite-box 3204, Folder 34)
    - Bolte, Gisela, 1976-1987 (Offsite-box 3204, Folder 35)
    - Bolte, Gisela, 1964-1982 (Offsite-box 3205, Folder 1)
    - Bolte, Gisela [RESTRICTED], 1968-1987 (Offsite-box R47)
    - Bonfante, Jordan, 1960-1982 (Offsite-box 3205, Folder 2-3)
    - Bonfante, Jordan [RESTRICTED], 1975-1982 (Offsite-box R47)
    - Bookman, George, 1959-1960 (Offsite-box 3205, Folder 4-5)
    - Borrell, John, 1980-1983 (Offsite-box 3205, Folder 6-7)
    - Borrell, John [RESTRICTED], 1982-1983 (Offsite-box R47)
    - Borrelli, Peter [RESTRICTED], 1969 (Offsite-box R47)
    - Bosemberg, Henry, 1948-1953 (Offsite-box 3205, Folder 8)
    - Boulat, Pierre, 1956-1957, 1967 (Offsite-box 3205, Folder 9)
    - Boulat, Pierre [RESTRICTED], 1956 (Offsite-box R47)
    - Bourgin, Simon, 1946-1956, 1963 (Offsite-box 3205, Folder 10-11)
    - Bourgin, Simon [RESTRICTED], 1961 (Offsite-box R47)
    - Bourke-White, Margaret, 1944-1952 (Offsite-box 3205, Folder 12)
    - Boyle, John, 1947-1974, undated (Offsite-box 3205, Folder 13-23)
    - Boyle, John, 1966-1968 (Offsite-box 3206, Folder 1)
    - Boyle, John [RESTRICTED], 1947, 1960-1965 (Offsite-box R47)
    - Bradley John H., 1969 (Offsite-box 3206, Folder 2)
    - Bralovic, Stoyan, 1956-1961 (Offsite-box 3206, Folder 3)
    - Brelis, Dean, 1950-1955, 1976-1983 (Offsite-box 3206, Folder 4-7)
    - Brelis, Dean [RESTRICTED], 1977-1983 (Offsite-box R47)
    - Brennan, Peter, 1942-1949 (Offsite-box 3206, Folder 8)
    - Brennan, Peter [RESTRICTED], 1949 (Offsite-box R47)
    - Briggs, Walter [RESTRICTED], 1982 (Offsite-box R47)
    - Bristol, Horace, 1946-1963 (Offsite-box 3206, Folder 9)
    - Bronn, Bruce, 1969-1970 (Offsite-box 3206, Folder 10)
    - Brooke, Edgar, 1946-1953 (Offsite-box 3206, Folder 11)
    - Brooks, Olice, 1951-1955, 1962 (Offsite-box 3206, Folder 12)
    - Brown, Gwilym S., 1967 (Offsite-box 3206, Folder 13)
    - Brown, John, 1972-1974 (Offsite-box 3206, Folder 14)
    - Brown, John [RESTRICTED], 1973 (Offsite-box R47)
    - Bryson, John, 1957-1961 (Offsite-box 3206, Folder 15)
    - Buantong, Aporanee, 1983-1984 (Offsite-box 3206, Folder 16)
    - Buantong, Aporanee [RESTRICTED], 1983 (Offsite-box R47)
    - Buist, Albert, 1979-1982 (Offsite-box 3206, Folder 17)
    - Buist, Albert [RESTRICTED], 1969-1982 (Offsite-box R47)
    - Burgin, Diane Josephy, 1969-1970 (Offsite-box 3206, Folder 18)
    - Burgin, Diane Josephy [RESTRICTED], 1966 (Offsite-box R47)
    - Burke, Donald, 1946-1965 (Offsite-box 3206, Folder 19-25)
    - Burke, James, 1947-1964 (Offsite-box 3206, Folder 26-30)
    - Burke, James, 1961-1965 (Offsite-box 3207, Folder 1)
    - Burke, James [RESTRICTED], 1959 (Offsite-box R47)
    - Burke, Jim: Accident File, 164-1966 (Offsite-box 3207, Folder 2)
    - Burke, Jim: Accident File [RESTRICTED], 1959-1964 (Offsite-box R47)
    - Burton, Sandra, 1970-1982 (Offsite-box 3207, Folder 3-4)
    - Burton, Sandra [RESTRICTED], 1970-1982 (Offsite-box R47)
    - Busch, Noel, 1944-1952 (Offsite-box 3207, Folder 5)
    - C: Miscellaneous, 1944-1963, 1970 (Offsite-box 3207, Folder 6)
    - Calhoun, Fill, 1943-1955 (Offsite-box 3207, Folder 7)
    - Campbell, Alexander, 1950-1965 (Offsite-box 3207, Folder 8-11)
    - Campbell, Alexander [RESTRICTED], undated (Offsite-box R47)
    - Campbell, Joyce, 1969 (Offsite-box 3207, Folder 12)
    - Campbell, Joyce [RESTRICTED], 1969-1970 (Offsite-box R47)
    - Canel, James, 1961-1962 (Offsite-box 3207, Folder 13)
    - Capa, Cornell, 1950-1956 (Offsite-box 3207, Folder 14)
    - Capa, Robert, 1954 (Offsite-box 3207, Folder 15)
    - Carig, Jeffrey [RESTRICTED], 1986 (Offsite-box R47)
    - Carney, Robert, 1983 (Offsite-box 3207, Folder 16)
    - Carney, Robert [RESTRICTED], 1983-1984 (Offsite-box R47)
    - Carty, Winthrop, 1956 (Offsite-box 3207, Folder 17)
    - Caruthers, Osgood, 1957 (Offsite-box 3207, Folder 18)
    - Cate, Merry Kay [RESTRICTED], 1981-1982 (Offsite-box R47)
    - Caturani, George, 1950, 1960 (Offsite-box 3207, Folder 19)
    - Cauley, Leslie [RESTRICTED], 1985-1986 (Offsite-box R47)
    - Chamberlin, Ann, 1956-1966 (Offsite-box 3207, Folder 20)
    - Champlin, Charles, 1959-1965 (Offsite-box 3207, Folder 21)
    - Champlin, Charles [RESTRICTED], 1962-1964 (Offsite-box R47)
    - Chandir, Riza, 1956-1958 (Offsite-box 3207, Folder 22)
    - Cheney, Elain Ruth Steinmetz Kelly, 1969-1970 (Offsite-box 3207, Folder 23)
    - Cheney, Elaine Ruth Steinmetz [RESTRICTED], 1969 (Offsite-box R47)
    - Chertow, Helen [RESTRICTED], 1982-1983 (Offsite-box R47)
    - Chickering, William, 1943-1947 (Offsite-box 3207, Folder 24)
    - Christopher, Robert, 1954-1955, 1961 (Offsite-box 3207, Folder 25)
    - Clark, Bennett Marsh, 1962-1963, 1970-1971, 1984 (Offsite-box 3207, Folder 26-27)
    - Clark, Bennett Marsh [RESTRICTED], 1962, 1984 (Offsite-box R47)
    - Clark, Edgar E., 1953-1966 (Offsite-box 3207, Folder 28)
    - Clark, Herbert, 1946 (Offsite-box 3207, Folder 29)
    - Clark, Marsh, 1964-1983 (Offsite-box 3207, Folder 30-33)
    - Clark, Marsh, 1969-1971, 1978-1984 (Offsite-box 3208, Folder 1-7)
    - Clark, Marsh [RESTRICTED], 1965-1985 (Offsite-box R47)
    - Clark, Marsh: Memorial, 1985 (Offsite-box 3208, Folder 8)
    - Clausen, Oliver, 1961-1965 (Offsite-box 3208, Folder 9)
    - Clausen, Oliver [RESTRICTED], 1960 (Offsite-box R47)
    - Clotfelter, James, 1964 (Offsite-box 3208, Folder 10)
    - Cloud, Stanley, 1968-1982 (Offsite-box 3208, Folder 11-12)
    - Cloud, Stanley W. [RESTRICTED], 1969 (Offsite-box R47)